

Ikshita Dasgupta

Angular UI/Nodejs backend/Mean Stack



Profile

Experienced in Restful APIs, cloud computing,
Responsive web pages, E-commerce, social media,
banking, healthcare domain, 3rd party API like
Google, facebook, payment gateway, MEAN stack,
Nginx server, Proxy server, NOSQL, SQL, Code version
control, Different web framework in Node.js and js.



Work History

2020-01 -Current

Web Developer

Esec Forte Technologies Pvt. Ltd

- Creating RESTful API for mobile application and web application.
- Designing web pages.
- Integration of APIs.
- Unit testing
- Deployment to the server.
- Reviewed code, debugging, issue fixing.
- Technology: node.js (express), MongoDB, MySQL, Bootstrap, ngx-bootsrap, Angular-8, Glt, AWS, GCP for project deployment, nginx server



Address

Bangalore

Phone

8431679265

E-mail

ikshitadg@gmail.com



HTML,Bootstrap,ngxbootstrap

Intermediate

Angular 7,8



Sql(MySQL),Sequlize



No SQL (MongoDB), mongoos

е



Node.js web

framework, express



Git



AWS (EC2, s3 bucket)



Intermediate

Nginx web server



Elementary

Docker



Elementary

2019-03 -2019-12

Full Stack Web Developer

Freelancer

- Enhancing the client's existing product features.
- Designing the web pages.
- Creating APIs according to requirement.
- Integrating the APIs with frontend.
- Technology: frontend-angular 5, backend node(express.js)

2018-07 -2019-03

Backend Node.js Developer

3Embed Software Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

- Implementation of server side logic.
- Implementation of unit test cases.
- Implementation of security and data protection.
- Design and implementation of data storage solutions.



Education

2014-06 -

AMC Engineering College,MCA

2017-08

2011-06 - A.G.C,B.Sc,Computer Science

2014-03

2009-03 - HSSC(12th)

2011-03

2008-06 - SSC(10th)

2009-03



Projects

bwm: DWM is the Admin panel web site for tracking the low birth weight child build for Rajasthan State. Client can analysis of different digital weighing machine's low birth weighted child data, can add district, block, facility, users and can link device with facility, can view child details, can analysis the data, can download report, can see the device synchronization history etc. url: http://dwm.rajpusht.in/

Tools and technology: node, mongodb, angular 8, bootstrap, ngx-bootstrap

Rajpusht Survey: Rajpusht Survey is the Admin panel web site for improving maternal and child health built for Rajasthan State where client can analysis officer's collected data from beneficiaries (pregnant women) and used to evaluate all the task like pregnant women and their child monitoring and growth of the child and child diet plan, vaccination etc

url: http://survey.rajpusht.in/

Tools and technology: node, mysql, angular 8,

bootstrap, ngx-bootstrap